

About Me

I have 6 years of experience as a shopify developer and digital marketer, as well as strong leadership skills and a track record of success. I'm currently looking for a position that will allow me to use my extensive skills and experience to find new clients and develop online strategies that will help businesses grow.



+8801609277655



Sharif298240@gmail.com



262/3B westagargoan sheree-bangla nagar, Dhaka-1207

Language

- English
- Hindi
- Bangali

Expertise

- Shopify (a-z)
- Digital Marketing
- SEO(Search Engine Optimisation)
- Google Analytics
- keyword Research
- Google Ads
- Facebook Ads
- Youtube
- Lead Generation & E-mail
 Marketing
- Social Media Marketing & Management

MOHAMMAD SHARIFUL ISLAM

Digital Marketer

Experience

Upwork talent 2020 - present

I am working on upwork as a freelance shopify developer and digital marketer since 2020.I worked with various famous companies across the world and I fulfilled my client demand perfectly within a short time.

Fiverr 2020 - present

I am working on fiverr as a freelance digital marketer since 2020.I provide various types of Digital marketing service like Pinterest marketing, Lead generation,E-mail Marketing,Google Ads, Facebook Ads etc.

Future it Institute Dhaka- Bangladesh 2018 - 2020

I worked for future it institute from 2018-2020. I worked there as a Digital Marketer. I tried my best to fulfill authorities demand with experience work.

Education

Zhengzhou University

Studying computer science 2021-present

Shaheed police smrity college

Completed HSC 2016 -2018

